Inventory of the Narodno-trudovoi soiuz samizdat collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Film, slides, and negatives, 1969-1990. (Box 73-76)
  - Film, 1976-1990 (Box 73-75)
    - 680/71. (Box 73)
      See also boxes 64, 66, and 67
    - 717/72-724/72. (Box 73)
      See also box 9
    - 868/75 (Box 73)
    - 888/75-889/75. (Box 73)
      See also box 11
    - 998/77 (Box 73)
    - 1000/77-1008/77 (Box 73)
    - 1055/78-1057/78 (Box 73)
    - 1069/78-1071/78 (Box 73)
    - 1072/78. (Box 74)
      See also box 15
    - 1076/78. (Box 74)
    - 1315/81-1316/81. (Box 74)
      See also box 20
    - 1329/81-1331/81. (Box 74)
    - 1335/81. (Box 74)
    - 1337/81-1343/81. (Box 74)
    - 1345/81. (Box 74)
    - 1347/81. (Box 74)
    - 1352/81. (Box 74)
      See also box 21
    - 1355/81-1356/81. (Box 74)
    - 1377/82-1379/82. (Box 74)
    - 1381/82-1384/82. (Box 74)
      See also boxes 21 and 59
    - 1392/82-1394/82. (Box 74)
    - 1396/82. (Box 74)
    - 1398/82. (Box 74)
    - 1414/82. (Box 74)
    - 2604/89. (Box 74)
      See also box 43
    - 1416/82-1422/82. (Box 74)
      See also box 22
    - 1427/82. (Box 74)
    - 1500/82-1507/82. (Box 74)
    - 1595/85. (Box 74)
      See also box 25
    - 1611/85-1613/85. (Box 74)
    - 1622/85. (Box 74)
    - 1732/87-1733/87. (Box 74)
      See also box 27
    - 1809/88. (Box 74)
      See also box 29
    - 2116/88. (Box 74)
      See also box 35
    - 2169/89-2172/89. (Box 74)
      See also box 36
    - 2199/89-2202/89. (Box 74)
    - 2309/89. (Box 74)
      See also box 38
    - 2395/89 (Box 74)
    - 2793/90. (Box 74)
      See also box 45
    - 2800/90-2808/90. (Box 74)
    - "Taina Bukharina," by G. Z. Saraikin, 1990 (Box 75)
    - Unidentified (Box 75)
  - Film reels, 1969-1974 (Box 75)
    - 531/69. (Box 75)
      See also box 58
    - 817/74. (Box 75)
    - 819/74. (Box 75)
      See also boxes 10 and 76
    - 821/74 (Box 75)
    - 821a/74 (Box 75)
  - Slides, 1974-1987 (Box 75)
    - 799/74. (Box 75)
      See also boxes 54 and 58
    - 1676/86. (Box 75)
      See also box 26
    - 1683/86 (Box 75)
    - 1727/87-1729/87. (Box 75)
    - Unidentified (Box 75)
  - Cut Negatives, 1970-1988 (Box 75)
    - 558/70. (Box 76)
      See also box 6
      Digital use copy available.
    - 672/71. (Box 76)
      See also box 8
    - 674/71. (Box 76)
    - 677/71. (Box 76)
      Digital use copy available (675/71, 677/71, 678/71).
    - 716/72 (Box 76)
    - 734/73. (Box 76)
    - 739/73 (Box 76)
    - 740/73 (Box 76)
    - 751/73-753/73. (Box 76)
      Digital use copies available.
    - 756/73-758/73. (Box 76)
      Digital use copies available (756/73, 759/73).
    - 760/73-766/73. (Box 76)
    - 793/74. (Box 76)
      See also box 10
    - 796/74. (Box 76)
      See also boxes 54 and 77
    - 797/74. (Box 76)
      See also box 56
    - 815/74. (Box 76)
    - 819/74. (Box 76)
      See also boxes 10 and 75
      Digital use copies available (819/74 and 831/74).
    - 835/74. (Box 76)
    - 892/7-895/75. (Box 76)
    - 925/76. (Box 76)
      See also box 55
    - 957/76. (Box 76)
      See also box 12
    - 978/77-982/77. (Box 76)
      See also box 13
    - 984/77-986/77. (Box 76)
    - 1020/77. (Box 76)
    - 1058/78 (Box 76)
    - 1219/79. (Box 76)
      See also box 18
    - 1323/81-1332/81. (Box 76)
    - 1614/85 (Box 76)
    - 1659/85 (Box 76)
    - 1682/86. (Box 76)
    - 1702/87 (Box 76)
      Digital use copy available (1702/87 and 1954/87).
    - 1951/88 (Box 76)
    - 1980/88-1985/88. (Box 76)
      See also box 32
    - 1996/88-1997/88. (Box 76)
    - Archives 1-6 (Box 76)
- Sound recordings, 1982-1988. (Box 77)
  Contains compact sound cassette tapes. Most of the recordings are available for use in digital format. Arranged by NTS number or title for unnumbered items
  - 1441/82. (Box 77)
    See also box 22. Use copy available, 2000c83_a_0003808_a01
  - 1482/82.1. (Box 77)
    Use copy available: 2000c83_a_0003802_a01
  - 1482/82.2. (Box 77)
    Use copy available: 2000c83_a_0003811_a01
  - 1701/87. (Box 77)
    See also box 27. Use copy available: 2000c83_a_0003800_a01
  - 1797/88. (Box 77)
    See also box 28
  - Interview with Valerii Abramkin (2 cassettes), 9/9/1988. (Box 77)
    Use copies available: 2000c83_a_0003790_a01_pt01; 2000c83_a_0003800_a01_pt02
  - "Pamiat'," Demonstratsiia v Moskve, vstrecha s B.N. El'tsynym (2 cassettes), 1988 (Box 77)
  - Unidentified records (Russian songs), (3 cassettes). (Box 77)
    Use copies available: 2000c83_a_0003786_a01_pt01; 2000c83_a_0003786_a01_pt02; 2000c83_a_0003786_a01_pt03
  Appendix
  Downloadable PDF file of the Item Inventory in Russian
  An itemized list in Russian matching the item number with a title and other information created by NTS and updated by Hoover Institution staff.